[Music]
all they can do
this
[Music]
assistant
dude
[Music]
thank you
is
[Music]
all right
that's what they say
[Music]
foreign
let me
know
[Music]
foreign
oh my God
[Music]
foreign
every moment I've been busy is the
moment
I don't wanna close my eyes
to miss you babe
what's this
sweet surrender
I can still understand this moment
forever
forever and ever
I don't wanna close my eyes
[Music]
that you dream
ing
[Music]
I'll share your lovely dreams
I've waited so it's so long for you to
write me
the pillow that you dream
don't you know
[Music]
something about yourself
welcome to the 2022 Prudential best HR
practices are very report launch and
awards Gala
good evening ladies and gentlemen
after the cocktails we just had
we can't even say good evening
good evening ladies and gentlemen
the way I am privileged to be standing
here
I think I expected a little bit more
when I said good evening because we are
here to win everyone here is a winner
apart from our bosses okay before I even
continue to serve you what we've served
was to be prepared for you today I want
to have the pleasure and the privilege
of introducing my
a gentleman who to me is a brother I
brother zoned him when we're working
together in minibus
so he's my brother and he's a friend and
if ever I'm hosting an event I want to
be standing next to Brian Blondo because
Mr Brian murundo even his ancestors so
and they were like we need to name this
man after an energy drink a traditional
energy drink so that is the Boost
anybody needs so let's put our hands
together guys as we welcome Mr Brian
molondo who I have the privilege of
ambassadoring Prudential with and he
makes me look tall believe it or not I
know I look a little bit taller today
because I stand here with Brian good
evening ladies and gentlemen
good evening ladies and gentlemen
how about you guys we are actually a big
difference we're a big deal don't joke
with us so we are going to do this again
and
where we do International gigs you leave
us here so right now like we are not
even now much when they introduce us out
of Uganda people club and celebrations
so Steve Jin play that intro again and
you're going to clap when we walk back
on stage
okay
so ladies and gentlemen
welcome to the 2022 Prudential best HR
practices a very broad launch and awards
Gala
[Music]
and I've seen a table that makes the
most noise I think you have an award
tonight
this is what I love most about this
evening that us the employees get to
reward our bosses
yeah it's the first time we can just
send you for a workshop you go and think
about yourself as a boss if you're
performing very well yeah but also I'd
like to warn HR managers tonight if you
don't go back to on Monday to your
office without an award
you my friend the employees will look at
you and say
or what I'm
waitaka pip
we need to put you on a pip p-i-p
okay Prudential
for you when you see yourself in five
years you fit here
that's German tonight we're gonna see
winners but at the end of the day if
you're here you're already a winner we
couldn't do this without the amazing
amazing leadership of prudentials say
warm handclap to Prudential
yes and throughout this night you're
going to hear the words of the people
who have partnered with us during this
journey uh if you have been thinking
about participating in the HR survey you
find out why tonight but also uh we are
not just you know your emcees tonight we
are also uh partners with Prudential
they call us brand ambassadors but we
prefer to call ourselves employees
because
look at the salary we will talk about
yes but we prefer to call ourselves
partners and I'm here with my partner
no my insurance plan is here yeah okay
that is called Mrs Manuela yeah Brian
malondo Manuela that is a cold day Pro
investor plan
I am the investor
yeah
and I like how Ali is true to the job
Ali we recognize your presence today
thank you so much for protecting our
investment over there
yes Ali please keep your insurance
policies to yourselves
gentlemen you know Anne they say that
a healthy human being
deserves 12 compliments a day
so please turn to someone near you
tell them something nice even if you're
lying and yes just tell them something
nice we need healthy people we are
Prudential we do help I am told we do
health and you're very tall tonight oh I
can't believe this Brian
oh
[Music]
implements a friend tell them they are
tall high heels are hard to wear yeah
yeah but a trick also if you come in
high heels and you they're kidding you
remove them if she has hair that is not
hers tell her it is nice it's okay she
paid heavily for it
if her nails look nice talk about them
yeah we do Health at Prudential so we
need healthy people yeah and I left my
insurance plan at home yeah so this is
and I'm so glad that he's safe no matter
what he does because of Prudential
all the time absolutely are we excited
to win tonight
are we excited to win tonight
I didn't know bosses could be afraid if
you are a boss whether you live younger
you haven't won your job is still there
so be excited everyone who is here is a
winner today absolutely hey tonight
we're going to have winners we're going
to have great food uh we have been
informed by the organizers that the
speeches are very short and they've also
informed us that the emcees look
absolutely elegant so yeah that's
reliable that's the night we are
celebrating tonight and I will ask the
fellow team to play us a music when we
come back we are officially starting uh
this even ladies and Gentlemen please
get yourself a drink of your choice and
welcome once again
gotta tell you a little something about
yourself
[Music]
[Applause]
wanna show you
[Music]
together
[Applause]
[Music]
treasure
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
you
I never told you that I love you
[Music]
waiting any longer
thank you DJ thank you so much and
without wasting any more time we are
going to continue this event by inviting
the most important person the one who
has hosted us here and I've been warned
that I edited Brian mulundo's Name by
adding that it is an energy drink and I
should leave people's names alone so I
will leave people's names alone
so let's put our hands together as we
welcome the CEO of Prudential Uganda
tete ITV
and he truly understood this event
ah I know your name my friend
[Music]
good evening ladies and gentlemen
thank you for making it to tonight's
event
to the representative of the Prime
Minister
about the excellencies pairs of missions
and Ambassador who's here
I'm the CEO of Prudential Africa
my own captains of industry who are here
I'm representative of the insurance
regulator Authority is the Sunday
potazio
and then all representatives from
government Ministries and departments
our invited guests ladies and gentlemen
allow me to express my utmost admiration
and respect to all of you
for how elegant you're looking tonight
and allow me to say
Bo
if I did what I deserve a round of
applause what you think so
it probably tells you how well I've
settled into this society and how much
I've embraced the Ugandan way of doing
things
and my love for this country is
unabated
it's a great privilege and honor to host
you to the second edition of the HR best
practices survey Gala where we celebrate
excellence in the workplace
to us in Prudential it's important that
we facilitate conversations about the
best human resource practices in Uganda
in Prudential with family believe that a
workplace epitomizes excellence
and so therefore given that individuals
spend the majority of their time in the
workplace whatever we have to do in
investing in the environment where
employees can Excel is actually
important to us
and we believe that there's a direct
correlation between a company's culture
and its ability to get the most out of
its employees where the culture is Right
Innovation is driven
productivity increases and employee
well-being is at the height that you
should be at
consequently our belief is that we
should encourage best HR practices in
this market
at Prudential we're devoted to
cultivating a culture that that
encourages employee Excellence a whole
culture of excellence and it makes us
invest in our employees in providing the
right training development and career
advancement opportunities and we offer a
supportive work environment that values
diversity inclusivity and collaboration
furthermore we are continuously evolving
and adapting to meet the changing needs
and aspiration of our employees
as our favorite desire that as we host
tonight's event will stimulate the right
kind of conversations that will drive
the right kind of behaviors and cause
employers to invest in their workplaces
to create the right environment for
employees to thrive and to excel
one of the surprising things I noticed
in Uganda when I arrived here is the
fact that many workplaces offer saccos
and graduity plans which are critical to
employees personal financial well-being
and we also cognizant to the fact that
numerous employees have invested in life
insurance policies and is our
responsibility to work collaboratively
with them to further solidify their
financial blueprint
by enabling employee deductions we
believe that you'd help in this big step
of taking care of your employees
financial future and ensure that we
build a strong financial base and Foster
resilience in families
in conclusion I would like to extend my
heartfelt congratulations to the
companies that will be recognized this
evening for the unwavering commitment to
best HR practices
your dedication to creating a workplace
of Excellence is not only inspiring but
also a Testament of the power of Human
Resources in driving business success
thank you all very much I hope you enjoy
the evening let's all face life together
till in our way
bigger round of applause ladies and
gentlemen
foreign
you have a Uganda name right
so
um
you you have a Uganda anymore
what does it mean I keep on giving life
a good life
who lied to you fire them
fire them
USI naturally means a winner
so I guess you're on the winning team by
being at Prudential sir
yes ladies and gentlemen
as you heard the CEO
Prudential turinawei
reverse life
together and throughout the night you
you can't even talk to each other about
the things that Prudential has done for
you for your children some of you have
uh already have set up investment
accounts with us you've done the pro edu
savior on the medipro and we are very
very glad because we are we couldn't
have done this without you so give
yourselves a big round of apples across
the room for believing in Prudential
as
an industry lead
you need people who believe in the
vision and not just at the country level
but at the global level
and we keep talking about Africa being
the New Frontier and you need very very
strong people to lead the discussions at
the group level ladies Gentlemen please
welcome with me the CEO of Prudential
Africa Mr Emmanuel mokobi
[Music]
I'm happy
first of all let me just say that um
TT
is a CEO of Prudential
Uganda
but that doesn't mean that you're the
boss
of this session the boss of this session
is the MCs
and I remember very well
they lay down the rules and the rule
says that all species might be very
short
I'm not sure your speech was that short
what I'll try to do is to try and then
align with the rules
ladies and gentlemen I'm very very
conscious of the fact that
I'm standing in the presence of very
distinguished
guest
and as such I need to recognize all of
that
so your excellencies the ambassadors
hair submissions
because CEO of Prudential life
Uganda
CEOs of other organizations gather here
colleague board of directors of
Prudential Life Assurance Ghana
representative from the insurance
regulatory Authority Mr Sunday putazio I
hope I got a name right
we also have representatives from
government Ministries and departments
all invited guests ladies and gentlemen
good evening
it's always an honor to be back here in
Uganda it's a country that I like
visiting
but most importantly
I'm really excited that I got the
invitation to come and join you
celebrate tonight
and on that note I would like to say a
very big thank you to Titi and the
management team of Prudential
for giving you the invitation for me to
be here tonight
as a company
we understand the importance
of Human Resources practice
in promoting the development in Africa
as a matter of fact
as a company
our purpose
is to make sure that we give people the
most out of life and this obviously
includes all of our employees
now it's because of this that we believe
that whenever you have a talented
Workforce
that feels appreciated and enabled
then what happens is that these ladies
and gentlemen
are able to bring
their possible best to work any day
and definitely when that happens
you realize that that is directly linked
to productivity of these individuals
and that is linked again to company
performance
and when that happens then a community
as a whole
benefits from that
now let me just say that Prudential is
very proud to be championing
this event
of good human resource practices in
Uganda
now it's because we recognize that
our people
are the most valuable asset that we have
now recently I did a real shoe
visiting all of ilb use
the objective there was really to
Cascade down
our strategy
now one of the things that I said on my
brochures was the fact that
strategy is easy for anybody at all to
come to copy your competency very very
easy to come
copy
now the I.T infrastructure that we lay
down in our companies
the office building and all of those
things when the company has money and
feel like getting all of those is very
easy to get
now what is very important
a very difficult you know to get is the
human resource and the reason is that we
are competing for good talents on the
same Market
now and therefore once you have very
good challenge in your organization
then at least you can do is to create
the enabling environment for these young
men and women to be able to pick
and realize they are individual dreams
now there can only be one Apollo
and we are fortunate to have Apollo here
with us as our board chair to be
difficult to replicate another Apollo
now
as a matter of fact if you attempt to
replicate Apollo what is going to end up
with is that you are going to have the
copy or the duplicate or the fake Apollo
and we'll be having the original Apollo
that's how difficult and important for
us to what you know focus on our human
resource and make sure that we create
the enabling management for them to be
able to to pick
now like I said
we we value that
and that's the more reason why
from investing in training and
development and promoting work life
balance you know we are dedicated or we
are dedicated yeah to providing our
employees with the right supports so
that they will be able to pick and
realize their personal
aspiration
ladies and gentlemen in addition to our
personal commitment
of this event
it's important for me to also realize or
mention here
that Prudential Africa is also a thought
leader
on many aspects of the things that
matter most for the people of Africa
we understand the unique challenges that
this region faces
and we are committed to finding
innovative solutions to address them
from Financial inclusion
to health care and to education we are
working to create a better future for
all Africans
just before I take my seats and I hope I
obey the rules there are two things I
would like to say
the first one
is that I would like to take this
opportunity to congratulate all winners
tonight
and to also go ahead to say that your
dedication to creating and supporting
and empowering work environment is truly
commendable and we are proud to have you
as our partners in promoting the
development in Africa
finally I would like to wish everyone
here tonight a good evening
let us continue to work together to
create a better future for ourselves
for our businesses and the communities
in which we serve thank you let's face
life together truly now we yeah
[Music]
I cannot not recognize the fact that
they've just served as food
and it was perfect timing because our
next speaker
is in Ramadan you guys so it was perfect
timing like when they had that it's time
for us to eat whatever it is they've
prepared for us
then they know that we are now inviting
our next guest who is
um
Mr uthman mayanja our country senior
partner because everyone that wants to
do anything amazing has to do it with an
amazing partner
to come on time
[Music]
thank you thank you very much
the representative of our chief guest
this evening
your excellencies and heads of mission
present
the regional chief executive for
Prudential Africa
chairman
of Prudential Assurance Uganda Limited
and members of your board present
the chief executive of Prudential
Assurance Uganda Limited
captains of industry present
HR directors
managers and professionals
Media Partners distinguished guests
ladies and gentlemen good evening
I do hope that to that very lengthy
protocol everyone feels they've been
covered in it
it was my intention
my role this evening is provide a high
level summary
of the survey process
and perhaps what I'll do
in all fairness is quite a bit a little
bit of your background my name is uthman
mayanja country senior partner price
hotels Coopers and we engage by
Prudential
to help to run the survey
and I'll tell you about the survey
process and I went through with
administering the survey collecting the
results and so on and so forth
I'll also use a minute or two to share a
few observations about the results the
feedback from the survey
and how some of that links in with what
we see as a Professional Services firm
so very briefly the survey process
involved us developing a questionnaire
14 thematic errors was selected and we
will be going through that through the
awards ceremony
and for each of those
14 thematic errors five questions were
developed and severe respondents were
required to rank
their response from a scale of one to
five five being
I strongly agree and one being do not
agree
um we shared a link to the questionnaire
which was electronic with HR managers
and directors
in each of the companies that we got in
touch with and the survey was open to
all Employers in Uganda obviously it's
not possible to find each and every
employer but we we got hold of the vast
majority of employers in the country
um
so hrl leaders are then required to
disseminate the link to employees
and encourage them to complete the
survey
we allowed a period of three weeks for
the survey to be completed and we did
extend that period because of the
holiday period and the survey closed
earlier on this this calendar year
um we then collected all the responses
and and this year we had a significant
increase in the number of respondents I
was about 60 percent increase in
response from the prior year
and analyze all those responses for each
of the Thematic areas and for each of
the employers
we also performed the high level
evaluation that allowed us to then come
up with the ranking by employer across
each thematic area
as well as understand what the feedback
is telling us now I know that we have an
award ceremony this evening and
it's a winner takes all sort of
environment and we are all waiting with
weighted breath to see who won
um my biggest takeaway personally is not
so much in one which award
my biggest check out is what I employee
is telling us employers about HR
practices for me that's a huge takeaway
and then I'd like to give a snippet of
what that looks like we all know that
2022 was started with a lot of optimism
in Uganda our economy was fully released
from Lockdown
um
three months later Russia did something
to somebody and things began to turn on
their heads and we've quickly found
ourselves from a huge optimism to
cautious optimism
we also find ourselves dealing with the
cost of living crisis if you like not
just in this country but around the
world and I think it's fair so that the
server went into the market with
employees feeling a little bit
apprehensive about a number of measures
in the way the the relationship between
employee and employer
I am pleased and it was pleasing for me
to see within the results
which for me if I'm after moving in the
right direction
one of the biggest indicators that HR
partitions look at is people engagement
how engaged employees with the company
and we saw an increase in engagement
index it's quite strong at 87 percent
and all the key components of people
engagement are quite High
in addition another key indicators
whether people intend to stay with the
organization for the next 12 months
and that's another index where again
people perform companies perform quite
well with an overall score of 85 percent
and the the details when we get into
details are more interesting it becomes
and I think I won't bore you because of
the supervisor has been given
and I should be the first one to make
the speeches very short for reasons that
the NC has explained very well
um
where we have seen some challenges and
areas to do the employee Wellness
which didn't do very well reward and
recognition remains will always be a
sticky point and we know that from
experience
um
and finally employee
[Music]
growth and public growth and development
to the scenario that didn't do very well
and for me those are areas that are also
quite important
um but I think the good news which I'll
come to in a moment
is when we have done separately PWS has
run a global CEO survey and the results
for East Africa for which we had more
than 200 responders within East Africa
um
look favorably upon the world the
prospects of their companies much more
than the global CEOs would reflect so
more than two-thirds of East African
CEOs are optimistic about growth in the
next 12 months as well as the
sustainability of their Enterprises over
the next 10 years
more importantly they see technology as
an emerging risk and something that
needs to be harnessed in order to
safeguard and enhance the chances of the
company's thriving over the next over
the next 10-year period
what is pleasing from an employee's
point of view is that CEOs unlike our
counterparts globally have no intentions
to reduce their Workforce so still
looking at growing their Workforce no
intentions to freeze spare or freeze
hiring so it's a very positive
environment from an HR point of view and
I think that is good news for us
if I look at the results around
um
digital upskilling for this for the
employees having now here in Uganda as
well as results for
if you look at the results for digital
upscaling and Innovation
employees have
assessed the employers quite favorably
it could be better but it's moving in
the right direction so they're not the
strongest scores but they're moving in
the right direction and that for me is a
strong indicator combined with a
maintained Focus around because you know
we come out of covered
with pay freezes and recruitment freezes
and we're not in a period where our CEOs
are feeling optimistic about investing
in people
at the same time recognizing the
challenge around sustainability being
dependent on how we harness technology
and now we upscale our people
therefore when I look at the results as
a whole to my mind I see a cup that is
half full rather than half empty and
gives a lot of optimism and I think the
message for HR leaders is you are
getting a lot of things right
you need to keep pushing and continue to
improve so that
the point that has been mentioned by
both mocopy and antete is really around
ensuring that your employees
bring their best to your organization
every day and bring their best fashion
of themselves and you enjoy that
productivity for the good of the company
thank you very much ladies and gentlemen
that's all I have prepared for you thank
you
[Music]
pick a round of applause for uthman
mayanja ladies gentlemen
thank you sir PWC made sure that
everything is right okay
we didn't have electoral Commission in
these things
if so you can't come here and say yeah
everything is what
legit
you know
it's Ramadan so uthman surprises me that
even after fasting for all these hours
he still has a deep voice
my friend
one of a kind
in a few minutes we're going to launch
the HR survey and of course start the
world night but as we do you've just
received the meal let's allowed the ban
to give us one or two songs to allow us
each and when we come back ladies
gentlemen we are starting the award
night Abi kaban
we've been in this crazy world
suckered up in these confusion nothing
needs to make easy
foreign
how to make a brighter day
[Music]
together
we can do it better
[Music]
only if we try
the troubles on our shoulders and
sometimes this seems so much
as they gotta be a solution
not to make a brighter day
front a little better
try a little more hotter than before
let's do what we can do together
only we can do it better
thank you
the sun is breaking away
that's the end of the day
[Music]
don't keep the things that don't show
everywhere
don't keep the days that don't show
as the two light turns to move the light
I'll be on my way
thank you
[Music]
foreign
I'm feeling it stronger stronger
I believe you and me we're falling in
love
[Music]
thank you
on Monday
[Music]
in my place when you know because maybe
this Friday me and you will be chilling
anymore
[Music]
done
oh yeah baby
[Music]
foreign
boys
[Music]
thank you
to use
[Music]
someone on my mama doesn't always
foreign
[Music]
you
know
[Music]
foreign
huh
[Music]
foreign
baby silly
[Music]
before
yes
[Music]
foreign
really good
[Music]
family
foreign
[Music]
get down
thank you
[Music]
sleeping on you
again
[Music]
foreign
yeah yeah
[Music]
indeed
to me
[Music]
foreign
classical
[Music]
don't go
all right
thank you very much pen on team ladies
and gentlemen I hope that you we have
all served dinner have we
have we served dinner
hello these people
okay have you served starters
[Music]
we have how many courses today we're
four four yeah
if you are single
and you're going to go back home and
sleep like a question mark
we encourage you
to pack
and also eat for tomorrow but also
also yeah because you
guys so a Muslim put them put your hand
up don't be shy
support that bro please
please yeah please just put up your hand
uh one of the people waiting on us will
ask you then whisper to them dark
point of view from a lemon's point of
view what today this evening is about
and then I realized that a chintu chakai
a Prudential
like when they say it's near the
stalkerish because they are with you
whether you know it or not and this is
why Prudential doesn't just care about
its clients no it cares about enough to
make sure your boss is encouraged to do
the right thing like absolutely what
they are supposed to do and they've gone
ahead to even put some rewards for your
bosses so that they treat you very well
yeah one
you know one day I I did an appraisal
um in one of the places I worked and and
you know I don't know why you still put
this question on the appraisal form
right I was asked what do you see
yourself in this company in five years
and I put
my boss's position
it's the last appraisal I did in that
company
when they are looking when they were
retrenching I was like Brian we know
you're talented but but
it's not you it's us
I was like all right
but the good thing now we are both in
the gig economy
that's gentlemen allow me recognize the
presence of the minister of Kampala
honorable
welcome sir
and on that note before we start the
award ceremony I'd like us to stand on
our feet and officially uh
uh
uh let's be outstanding for the anthems
and we'll start
the awards ceremony thank you
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
thank you
I give you money if you can say one word
East African
okay
we need to learn that anthem
We're Young are we here
very good
ladies and gentlemen it's now time to a
what are you ready
are you ready
and it does not matter which award you
get whether it's the first or the rest
they are all equally important yes no
yes we are not starting with short ones
or third ones
and then we have a little just small
brief when you receive your award don't
be concerned when we come and pick it
from you so that we pack it properly for
you as you
exitia we want to be taking your Awards
you'll come and pick it up and when you
see it if we come for it it's not
because we are taking it we just want to
make it so that as you enter home you
enter like a winner
foreign
also if you get an opportunity to speak
at the microphone please keep your
speech very short otherwise we shall
Grammy Award you
bring your microphone close to your
mouth so that we hear all the
appreciation appreciate everyone yeah
you know how you start appreciating them
maybe at home who doesn't even know you
have an insurance policy thank all of
them just it's your chance to thank but
to the microphone I encourage if you're
born again and you receive an award
please when you come here don't say
about God don't give us a testimony we
already know you're happy yeah we know
that it's God who did it okay
all right are we ready we are ready very
good
no no no introduce yourself here and you
have one don't be shy tell us who are
you are you in a relationship are you
happy if you are not happy it's just to
know that you are in it but you are not
happy so that we can help so introduce
yourself completely are you single are
you attached are you in a situation we
need to know your statuses yeah you know
how do we get you today fantastic
[Music]
all right this is it ladies and
gentlemen
I'd like to welcome
uh the first presenter of the first
category tonight let me tell you a short
story about this man
I absolutely
yeah I absolutely this guy this guy is a
cool guy cool like he's a really dope
guy like he bounces like he's gonna
bounce yes but you know those men when
you look at them
and
you say
I wish my mother tells me Brian that is
your father
can forgive my mother
I can just tell my mother Mama the devil
is a liar
he's such a a fantastic man but what
made me like really have a lot of
respect for him
he embarks on a project
that is very very very very passionate
about the project that is geared towards
naming all our roads
Uganda names
all our roads
but foreign requisition as he's doing
that can you talk to Google so that if
I'm going to come watch I'm not being
told that I'm going to key I'm okay okay
can they put like a muganda
that is the exactly they are giving
directions they are going to name a name
before you know it people can't see me
properly as it pronounces my name so
while we are so so excited that he
embarked on such a passionate project we
wish him all that act yes I think the
voice will be us us and we are pitching
that job
foreign so I love this project and you
know what if you saw if you ever wish to
co-opt us we are willing and available
very good
after that we can talk
but he doesn't just do this he's a
lawyer he's also the board chair of
Prudential Uganda this gentlemen welcome
oht1 Apple maccubia
thank you
I don't know
in the Thematic area of company
performance and confidence this is what
made your organization stand out
the organization has clearly
communicated its vision mission and
values to its staff the organization
strategy and direction are properly
articulated and communicated in
employees understanding and relating to
their departmental strategies the
leaders of the organization leaving the
organization's values
the organization that demonstrated best
practices in the Thematic area of
company performance and confidence is
okay I was hoping that they will be
showing the runners-up and so on
but ladies and gentlemen a good evening
to you all
and the winner of the company
performance and confidence is
guess who
me net
[Music]
protections
well done minute group
minute has only two employees
what is the HR one is the finance
all right
a picture congratulations
we are in the business of risk advisory
and insurance we are glad to see most of
our clients and our partners here thank
you so much for honoring what we do and
considering it's the stuff that voted
this is Testament of uh employee value
proposition and we are glad thank you so
much fantastic
gorgeous
[Music]
the ladies to find their seat I just
realized that it's not a must even if I
stand up there I'm not told I cannot
deceive you into thinking anything so
before I tear this dress before I return
it insurance doesn't allow me to return
it spoiled
I will have to call the next gentleman
whose name I love
jejetan that's a very nice name region
our regional director that's a very nice
and I will whistle as his work as they
are working it's a she
God JJ
ah clap for JJ guys
oh my God in the Thematic area of reward
and recognition this is what made your
company Stand Out employees have good
understanding of how their pay is
determined are recognized in a way that
motivates them their compensation keeps
up with the rising cost of living
expenses the organization's benefit
plans are competitive with those offered
by other similar organizations
the organization that demonstrated the
best practices in the Thematic area of
reward and recognition is
Uganda Brewer is limited
[Music]
I think all of us should also go on the
stage as customers
hey
thank you
this one must be the chief tester never
joke with a man with suspenders
[Music]
so smart
wow thank you thank you it is such an
honor to be here that I actually wanted
the team to talk but they want me to
talk on their behalf so on behalf of
Uganda breweries limited it is the
people who have made this possible for
us we thank you we take this with so
much pride as usual and we just want to
say thank you very much
thank you very much
very good
[Music]
my temperature
but now I'd like to welcome
to give out the award for employee
engagement and enablement the executive
administration at the bank of Uganda Mr
John shamongez
in the Thematic area of Employee
Engagement and enablement this is what
made the organization Stand Out
employees are proud to work for this
organization and would recommend it as a
great place to work majority of the
employees intend to stay with the
organization for at least another 12
months employees are willing to go
beyond what is expected for the success
of the organization the organization
that demonstrated best practices in the
Thematic area of Employee Engagement and
enablement is
a very good evening to you ladies and
gentlemen
the winner of the employee engagement
and enablement
best practices
I'm not sure whether I'm reading it
right
I need to con
consult Brian
okay this is Brand's words not mine
Uganda Brewer is limited questions
[Music]
okay good evening ladies and gentlemen
it's really exciting first of all I must
say we are so happy to have yet another
recognition it's not by accident
we take staff and our people seriously I
must say thank you for recognizing us
and this we are dedicating to our staff
people are the most important resource
for us and therefore Uganda Brothers
celebrating life every day everywhere
yeah
can I help you with the problem
s
[Music]
congratulations congratulations
party
looks like you're in a very winning
spree
sorry sorry
Uganda breweries oh my goodness but
congratulations anyway something has
happened that's why I'm even thinking
things that are not here breaking news
we have an important guest that has to
be recognized yeah
Prudential Cameroon now
this gentleman's name is Mister you
people don't know drumroll drumroll drum
roll
next gentlemen but you guys this is not
a pet name from me but he's called Mr
Handsome brain
you guys Mr please let me tell you
no someone is handsome and they know
their brain is important
they cover it they protect it for us
ours is out there but he protects these
it's very nice to meet you Mr Handsome
[Music]
you're welcome
oh and then okay of course without
wasting any time we call back our CEO
from Prudential I sorry no
no
um
to come and give the award for quality
and innovation
in the Thematic area of quality and
Innovation this is what made your
organization stand out the organization
has put in place systems and processes
to enable its employees work effectively
the leadership team recognizes that
quality and Innovation are top
priorities employees are encouraged and
supported to be Innovative in their
workplace and their contribution to
Quality and Innovations is recognized
during the performance evaluation the
organization that demonstrated best
practices in the Thematic area of
quality and Innovation is
and the winner is
simpler qci access to quality affordable
medicines
[Music]
all right
well done
[Music]
recognition now we are here for quality
my CEO is in a meeting and I'm now
managing
we are purpose inspired
we are responsibilities centered we are
Excellence focused we are innovating
driven we are integrity and trusty
anchored we are committed to you to our
stakeholders
are everyone and the community we are
really very very grateful with me is the
company pharmacist
with me the head of Finance with me is
the head of quality and I hear the
people thank you ah
tell your neighbor
what are you
[Music]
that works like
panado extra extra
and what was your school motto uh okay
the one of kabari primary was
just people are Integrity driven you are
aiming
it was so to reap then would add
just mine was
um
again
we are Integrity driven Innovation what
there's a word he used will Google it
yeah at least I know that CEO wherever
you have finished that meeting
foreign
all right we'll now go into employee
Wellness to help us give up this award
Mr Patrick okero for the office of the
Prime Minister it's a commissioner for
human resources
in the Thematic area of employee
Wellness this is what made your
organization Stand Out employee
well-being is highly prioritized in this
organization and employees can find
balance between work and their personal
lives the organization has implemented
various programs on my well-being
including but not limited to physical
emotional social and financial
well-being
the organization that demonstrated best
practices in the Thematic area of
employee Wellness is
guess
the employee Wellness winner is
minute
[Music]
oh my God oh God
why the employee resigned
countries a lot okay okay
[Music]
those hey there is a missing minute
I want the full package
very good
[Music]
well done well done minutes
congratulations
once again sorry we were shocked and
joyous the last time I didn't get to
introduce us she's Caro a Theo she hates
our business development and marketing
my name is Doreen Mulia I am the head of
Human Resources we are glad for this
recognition
we are all aware the effects that kovid
had on us and there's nothing it
affected so much as our well-being
especially the mental well-being and we
are glad that we're able to put in place
avenues for our employees to get support
thank you again for recognizing us and
have a lovely evening thank you thank
you so much wow congratulations
foreign
she's the one walking in front that one
yeah she used to be very intelligent
because as if it means anything you know
someone who makes you feel like with
your son might be the reverse yeah
she was so intelligent because she's the
first before they should read results
Doreen
and if you have a child like Doreen you
have to train yourself to speak when
they win
I'm sure I'm going to have trouble I'm
so glad we haven't met anyone who is
Happy enough to cry here but as
expecting but to be emotional I receive
their Awards
so let's just hold our breath and call
Mr uthman my angel again
so that he helps us give out the award
for diversity and inclusion Hajj
magic area of diversity and inclusion
this is what made your organization
stand out
the leadership team has created a
diverse and inclusive culture and work
environment their adequate gender
representation at the top level all
employees are treated as individuals
regardless of their job age race gender
physical capabilities and so much more
the organization that demonstrated best
practices in the Thematic area of
diversity and inclusion is
the winner for the 2022 Prudential HR
best practices survey for diversity and
inclusion is stanbic Bank
hey the CE is also here if you don't
want to be fired you better come
yes sir
[Music]
uh-huh in the middle there
the HR David
I think I should also come and stand
there
I work with you good evening Brian good
evening sir
your paycheck is still with Mr McCarter
um
wow excited but I think for a man to be
receiving this
in an uninclusive world is a bit of a
right yeah so
if I could invite
the ladies to say something
but we're really really excited
important and as they said we talk about
mental Financial
diversity and all those so thank you so
much
all right congratulations San big Bank
of guys gentlemen
[Music]
well done
now I'd like to also uh just you know
say this a disclaimer
the boat chair
and the CE of the bank but uh let's give
the birthday a round of applause for
being discreet
he never disclosed
a the CE was shocked
to hear that they've won so I thank you
sir
all right
uh also if you're speaking please move
closer to the mic so we can capture
everything all right now to present
Learning and Development please welcome
with me if just introduced a new course
uh on mindset change and I think we all
need that as a nation uh the DVC Finance
from Michael University Professor
engineer Henry Arena Three welcome sir
in the Thematic area of Learning and
Development this is what made the
organization stand out all employees
have access to care growth opportunities
and receive adequate support from their
managers to further their career
aspirations employees have access to the
Learning and Development that they need
to do their work and given an
opportunity to apply these skills
the organization that demonstrated best
practices in the Thematic area of
Learning and Development is
[Music]
hey hey
foreign
[Music]
thank you for giving employees an
opportunity to give the employers
feedback I am still shocked
um at Absa our people are asking and we
believe that they enable us to deliver
our strategy and so this award we
receive it as a testament that our
people have trust in the efforts that
the people team people management team
and also the Senior Management have
implemented in enabling them to grow
thank you so much
well done Absa
that's African City
that's Absa
[Music]
assist
in the Premier League
[Music]
well done guys
that it's a team of women in this month
of women
and um
okay it's it's interesting that this
gentleman is coming to give out an award
to celebrate to reward workplace culture
and environment because I have never
seen someone who is as friendly
as welcoming
as we're not going to be a relationship
like trying to get clients to get what
they want this gentleman is became my
friend before I know how important he
was and if you're his friend you call
him s but today I want to risk and say
his name he is
regional chief officer please stand up
please come and give out this award with
us
I committee
eat my tongue and the Thematic area of
workplace culture and environment
this is what made your organization
stand out
the workplace designs are functional
friendly engaging and innovating and the
organization makes psychosocial support
available to staff the organization also
has implemented effective systems for
keeping remote employees connected the
organization that demonstrated best
practices in the Thematic area of
workplace culture and environment is
thank you
firstly good evening everyone I'm happy
to be back to my old home it's exciting
to see the the stuff that is improved in
the last 12 months so I'm impressed TT
well done and to the board chair
I'm not sure if I'm bringing the right
award because my card says Learning and
Development so I don't know if that's
the same award
so the winner for Learning and
Development is simpler enough
[Music]
Make You Dance
well done
hey
[Music]
fantastic well done simpler
quality chemicals
[Music]
[Applause]
wow
this time I'm delegating
ah
hello everyone
thank you Prudential thank you for
um this award at cipla qcil we value
Learning and Development for employees
because it increases their knowledge
base and then that increases
productivity it increases quality it
increases efficiency and morale at work
so we're grateful that our employees
also appreciating the management team
for such efforts so thank you so much
well done well done
[Music]
well done
all right
stupid
hold it
now this is now literally a requirement
for most companies right in fact best
employers are encouraged to have a
division for ESG
as a requirement and right you know I
see my friend they uh
ESG means environmental social and
governance
yeah so bring it up in conversation you
know the EST of the yeah just bring it
up I'll meet you at ESG time fantastic
it is important and that's why we are
giving out this award tonight to help us
give it out Emmanuel deitumi the
president of human capital International
in the Thematic area of environmental
social and governance ESG compliance
this is what made the organization stand
out the organization has an ESG strategy
that is enabled in the organization's
culture and the leadership team has
demonstrated commitment and support
around ESG issues the organization has
been part of as well as supported
various Community Development programs
the organization that demonstrated best
practices in the Thematic area of
environmental social and governance ESG
compliance is sorry about the mix-up
let's welcome the deputy CEO of Next
Media Services Mr Joe chigozie
[Music]
good evening ladies and gentlemen
my name is Joe chigozie I represent Next
Media
on behalf of my group CEO I'd like to
say that thank you Prudential
for a very
good job
of course to present
the 2022
Prudential based practices
survey
for environmental social and governance
ESG compliance
and the winner
wow
who wants to join me to announce the
winner
the winner is
MTN
[Music]
Uganda
welcome MTN
a
bonjour MTN
Uganda
is back in uh supporting the Uganda
cranes
hey
[Music]
well done
good evening
ladies and gentlemen
Prudential for recognizing
us for environmental social and
governance
I think what we do about the environment
many things we are digital now
you know we no longer have
scratch cards that is about environment
also our must uh
friendly that is about environment
social
we are talking about
we are talking about the communities we
work with
and also governance one of the themes
that we are focusing on today we lost as
a
sponsors of Uganda cranes but we are
good together that is our theme for the
governance so thank you very much and we
thank you
fantastic
congratulations MTN Uganda
congratulations MTN once again and to
give out the next award we welcome Mrs
Irene kaguase the executive director
Uganda commission
I am already distracted I cannot wait to
see you up there we first go and go
super a little bit it's all right
in the Thematic area of digital
acceleration or upscaling this is what
made your organization stand out this
organization has put in place
significant Technologies to enable the
employees to deliver on his mandate all
employees have been part of the various
digital upscaling programs that the
organization has implemented employees
also feel that the organization has
prepared them to meet the skills
required to operate in this digital
world
the organization that demonstrates best
practices in the Thematic area of
digital acceleration or upskilling is
ladies and gentlemen
and the winner of the dicto acceleration
and upskilling is
Standard Chartered
[Music]
foreign
well done
thank you very much Brian and thank you
Prudential thank you ladies and
gentlemen
we are Standard Chartered Bank
your digital Bank
and for our staff we enable them to
learn from a digital platform that we
run in-house called discover where the S
and C is Standard Chartered so we have
loaded the content that we believe is
sufficient for our staff to equip them
with the skills they need for the future
so once again ladies and gentlemen thank
you very very much
and let's celebrate this win enjoy
[Music]
hey
their banking Hall is crazy man you
enter they give your number then you sit
where we enter
ah they first call you
but the good thing they also have coffee
in the lounge
so you first have uh is it Enduro and
Europe coffee well done well done yeah
banking holes oh
so please don't stop serving them
sometimes you can when you know for us
Hustlers you can walk through the city
now you're looking for what to do and
then you just enter a branch
hello welcome
please you are you are crediting or
debiting
then you're like ah I'm going to bulk
balcash now you first sit there where
there's enough AC water please don't
make sure you suffer is that is customer
Wellness
discuss yeah so you guys just do these
things but it should be to call it
that's why that's why even if you write
our names in the papers that we have
dormant accounts we shall not close them
foreign
fantastic are we are we fine are we
having a great time
we are winning right tap your name but
wake them up wake them up wake them up
check on them check on them yeah all
right
now to
award the performance and talent
management award please help me welcome
the Sea of Prudential Cameroon Mr
Handsome brain
in the Thematic area of performance and
talent management this is what made your
organization Stand Out employees have a
broad understanding of the talent
management practices within the
organization as well as how their
performance is evaluating employees are
provided with the right progression
opportunities and strongly agreed that
promotion and advancement opportunities
are awarded to the most qualified
employees the organization that
demonstrated best practices in the
Thematic area of performance and talent
management is
good evening everyone
this is Africa in miniature that's
Cameroon I uh
I'm quite comfortable in Uganda because
I see a lot of similarities between
Uganda and Cameroon by the way he said
almost everything in Africa is found in
Cameroon so everywhere I find myself in
Africa I feel at home
performance and talent management winner
goes to
wow
Uganda Brewery limited up
[Music]
foreign
is a very good employee employer
and our employees are fully engaged and
happy challenge is something that we
take seriously and we have devoted a lot
of time to come up with really good
strategies to grow internal Talent so we
are very happy about this and thank you
very much
all right
alcohol doesn't lie
all right your picture your picture
beautiful
[Music]
dance
they give you more
yes it's definitely working I've also
just noticed something that among these
winners we
[Music]
um
the dancing
shoes
no no no no no no please when you come
here represent because I'm beginning to
feel like I'm here alone
on that note you know sometimes you
enter a place when you're sure how short
you are like you know your shorty
whereas they kill you throughout the
night but you insist this lady I'm going
to call to they really made me feel a
little bit shorter sometimes you just
stand around the people and you feel
like really you cannot fall even if they
come in you can't fall down so this
giving out the next award is Mrs Maria
shipiri who is the chief human resource
officer Prudential Africa you see for
yourself
see see for yourself I want you to see
that I have suffered this even Don't
Come Close people will compare I don't
know Sports compare just to go and give
out the award we've already allowed in
the Thematic area employee growth and
development this is what made the
organization stand out this organization
has put in place an efficient and
effective mentoring and coaching system
all the employees have a career coach
that supports them to grow in their
careers the feedback system in place has
helped employees make immediate
Improvement in their performance
the organization that demonstrated best
practices in the Thematic area of
employee growth and development is
no rigging or anything of the sort no
alcohol
and the winner goes to graphic systems
Limited
congratulations
[Music]
later
graphic systems
[Music]
okay for one minute I thought we were
not getting one
this pressure is not good at all
this is terrible
Prudential thank you
would like to thank God
but most especially would like to thank
our staff
we dedicate this to our staff
our directors who are so dedicated
to seeing that the staff
grew
better at what they do with me is Kathy
head of marketing
and sabita who is head of recovery would
like to thank you so much God bless you
[Music]
well done graphic systems
oh
today yeah
you are like that but be
patients
you told you told the CEO that you
handed in the report oh
it's pressure is not good
just call the next person what
gentlemen
please help us welcome
it's probably the tallest man in the
room
David
to present the organizational policy and
process Effectiveness award
in the Thematic area of organizational
policy or process Effectiveness this is
what made the organization stand out the
organization creates awareness about the
key policies or processes these policies
are followed by everyone and action
taken for non-compliance the
organization's culture supports
collaboration for example working
together sharing knowledge and more
across various departments
the organization that demonstrated best
practices in the Thematic area of
organizational policy or process
Effectiveness is
a sign that there's some magic in the
luzira area because there's quite a few
minutes there no no no no
uh graphic systems
[Music]
it's no longer that
confidence is back
thank you so much Prudential thank you
so much for giving us an opportunity to
to forgiving our employers employees an
opportunity to have us evaluate them
and also to have them improve because
this helps them improve or applaud
themselves for being good employers so
thank you thank you so much
congratulations
yeah not shy at all congratulations
graphic systems
is doing well but did you say
David
hey David is so tall he can see tomorrow
David how's tomorrow we come
very good
very good well done
Nelson or match the director of of
business management ah he's very smart
I've been trying to tell him the whole
evening then I remembered that that is
um
so let's give it up for
is very smart this evening and I have in
the Thematic area of organization
agility and change management this is
what made the organization Stand Out
change management is a priority in this
organization and when change will cause
there are proper tools and training to
support employees to adopt the new
change all changes are communicated to
everyone prior to their occurrence
the organization that demonstrated best
practices in the Thematic area of
organization agility and change
management is
send me back
stanbic Bank
[Music]
s
indeed it can be
lightning like twice
uh
once again Prudential everyone here
thank you very much my name is David
mutaka and I lead the people and culture
team
this is really an exciting hour to win
we've gone through quite a bit of change
in the last
three years
trying to become the organization that
can truly Drive
uganda's growth
and to get this award with all the what
people have gone through in those three
years I think is Testament to the work
done and the resilience of our people
and Mr Mayan just spoke about what
happened in 2022 and how people have
shown that they can really rise the
occasion and that's what has kept us
going thank you very much
ah
[Music]
Bank
s
[Music]
so now you know we have to keep your
money here
you know yeah
agility
agility is very critical
especially in these times you know I
have I have and I'm not just saying this
because you know I have the privilege of
of working with Stan big bank on
probably one of the most impactful
projects for me because for us you know
every morning I speak to about five
million people every morning
on radio every morning
kids want to be like us they love us
they love what we do when they see us on
Instagram and we're doing all this
they're like oh my god when I grow up I
want to be like Brian yeah you know and
we have for the past eight years
I've had the privilege of going with
stanbic out to the schools every year
and changing the lives of schools of
students of teachers
and I'm telling you you guys and I I
talked to someone and say I don't just
want Banks to take my money
Banks should change people's lives
yeah yeah
so when we see you in education and
you're not just doing some you know
fancy CSR project and you're ticking the
Box you're actually changing people's
lives you know like it's it's probably
and I want to say this to you and it is
one of
the best
uh purposes of my life
I'm telling you uh Brian they're going
to promote you
I'm telling you I'm not yeah I'm
honestly I'm the stanbic national
schools Championship we just you know uh
uh rolled out a new season
and it's not even about winning money or
a trip or a solar system or whatever you
see kids because all of us have gone
through that when you're bullied doing
you don't have confidence you see all
these things and I have had to you know
cry with these kids because they can't
present and it's really magical and so
for me I go into these things like a
parent they are now like my kids you
know I see them and
I think wherever you work whether it's a
bank whether it is an insurance company
whether it is simpler you need to change
your communities
you must change your communities because
the communities will bring the money to
you willingly
yeah so give yourselves a big round of
apples if you're doing work with your
communities man so when you see us out
there in your schools welcomers
welcomers right
all right now they get a lot of flack
for
for not doing right
they are the child poster of
inefficiency who in fact most people
said I don't want to be a public servant
yeah
but you know what
we all know that you cannot do business
without government no you must have
government on your side right and there
are actually many government agencies
that do a great job
and tonight we are honoring the best
government agency
yeah and to help us give out this award
let me welcome the minister of Kampala
to give out the award to the best
government agency
[Music]
Brian
I don't know if I can say the winner
but the taker of their word
is Uganda
retirement benefits regulatory Authority
and I believe everybody
we reach that level
[Music]
um
congratulations
[Music]
thank you so much for recognizing us
when we do things quietly
we don't know that people recognize our
efforts
the journey
has not been smooth
transforming this sector and putting it
where it is today it is because of your
support and the good leadership that we
have thank you for your support and may
God bless you
another round of applause for ubra
well done
and now let's listen
to the remarks
of our chief guest the minister of
Kampala honorable to Gabi
welcome sir
thank you very much uh bran and my
little sister
I doubt if she is not an
but I'm not the chief guest the chief
guest is the right honorable
prime minister
Robina nabanja
who somehow is in me
so Kawaii might not be here
please listen to the speech from right
honorable prime minister
and perhaps allow me to be the prime
minister of this evening in this place
the CEOs and heads of organizations
the CEO
Prudential Africa
representatives of Prudential Uganda and
patina companies
representatives of uh from government
Ministries
departments and agencies
or invited guests
ladies and gentlemen
I apologize for the last three years
I didn't get a cough
unfortunately when I became relaxed with
the mask
the problem
somehow I saw it happening few days ago
that's why I had to go back to the mask
and to warn you people
but please put on your masks
the struggle is still on
we've not yet won the war
despite the fact that we won the battle
I'm pleased to join you at the 2022
Prudential best HR practices survey
launch and awards Gala
I'm particularly excited that we are
launching our port
that is going to hope all heads of
organizations
and human resources
in both the private
and public sectors
whom we believe will learn about good
Employment Practices thank you very much
employment is Central
to uganda's socio-economic
transformation and development
agenda
from the peasantry to a modern and
prosperous country
one of the main assets
of our young population
is labor
is you aware is part of the factors of
production
is skilled and productive labor force
contribute significantly towards a
dynamic and cohesive society and better
quality of life
the government is aware of the need to
ensure productive and decent
employment
for Ugandan citizens
article 40 of that constitution of the
Republic of Uganda spills out the
economic rights of every person in
employment or engaged in any form of
work
it calls for the passing of laws that
provide for the right of persons to work
under suitable
safe and health conditions
and ensure equal pay
for equal work without discrimination
it also states that every worker
should be allowed to rest and work for
reasonable hours
as well as enjoy holidays with the pay
practices such as this comprise the best
HR practices
as you may have be aware
the government developed Vision 2040
to put into action the national vision
statement
I read in quotes
it transformed the Ugandan Society from
a peasant to a modern and prosperous
country
within 30 years
on the progress that has been made
in addressing the challenges
affecting uganda's
socio-economic development since
Independence in 1962.
some of these challenges include
under development
of Human Resources
inadequate infrastructure
a small Market
lack of industrialization
and underdeveloped services sector
however
these challenges can be can better be
addressed
if Government and private sector
work together
the Prudential based HR practices survey
shows the commitment of the private
sector
to achieve
this agenda
the objective of Workforce Development
is not just to ensure business growth
but also to create prosperity
for individuals
businesses
and communities at Large
I did offer at all employers to embrace
the feedback your employees
offered in this survey
I thank every organization represented
here
today for participating in this survey
your participation shows your commitment
towards enabling ugandans
to strive in your workplaces
I thank you especially
the winners of the various categories
and perhaps
those who might have
leaked elections to take more than one
trophy
congratulations
Uganda breweries
who are my divorced friends we divorced
a few years a few months ago
congratulations
graphic Solutions
and I wonder where is Prudential
lastly
I would like to recognize and express my
appreciation towards Prudential for
showing leadership
and for mobilizing various Industries
to embrace this course
involving Human Resources practices
as I conclude I also thank you
for knowing the fact that much as the
private sector
is developing and growing the human
resources
all these human resources at the end of
the day are Guided by the public sector
so thank you very much for
recognizing the Uganda retirement
benefits registrationally Authority get
up for yourselves
and thank you very much for appreciating
the role of government in the human
resource development
I also thank all stakeholders who have
made this event a success get up for
yourselves
since I'm not a no coutinho allow me
with this remarks
to wish and to officially launch the
Prudential
best
HR practices survey
two zero two two
report
I thank you all for good and my country
a big round of applause for honorable
honorable will encourage you to stay
there and welcome Tete
also a board chair which diva Apollo
and efficacy of Prudential to please
join the Minnesota stage
a man walks down the street he says why
am I soft in the middle now why am I
soft in the middle also most of my life
joining
Redemption
[Music]
so Gentlemen please come closer
um be in the middle some of you the
other side
because we are doing something
hollywood-like so I yes this side
uh honorable this side
let's leave some space here or HD right
there because uh this is Hollywood like
the past of its kind
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you
yes
me says Maria shapiri the Chief Human
Resources
of his sack Prudential Africa also joins
right there in the middle
ladies and gentlemen yes
yes
and
we shall have
a show
of the launch of the report fast The
Honorable Minister will come and sign
and we shall have the Chief Human
Resources officer potential Africa to
also come and sign
and will have officially launched the
report imagine when you're in charge and
your bride comes down like that
[Music]
yes can we
honorable
foreign
[Music]
Georgia Georgia
well also welcome
the Sea of Prudential Africa
[Music]
now welcome
us
PWC who did a fantastic job making sure
that the results are legit
yes
and of course the man
giving leadership
Prudential Uganda today
yes well done
thank you thank you
I'm gonna request you to please stay
there
because that's German right now
we are going to be awarding the overall
winner
pressure
so let's uh let's let's uh
I think go to the center of the stage
so that so they break different things
without you and you don't perform like a
winner fantastic I expect you to be
happy a little bit more happy
fantastic so please
gentlemen lights camera action
overall the organization that
demonstrated the best HR practices
overall is
yeah
of course should be one of you
first of all all of you are winners
and all of you've been overall winners
because some of you've even made me come
here at this hour
what did I say the overload the winner
was wearing a novel The Winner who is
wearing an overflow according to
anikaansime is none other than oh my God
again
okay get up for yourselves again
[Music]
since you don't know how to sing
you can start celebrating when I read
actually let me say I read this and you
repeat you
you got uh
because uganda's word isn't it yeah so
Uganda
what is the next letter of alphabets
the 20th later
wow
[Music]
baby congratulations
I wanna
dance
way
[Music]
I think oh I suspected speech
speech
ers
[Music]
congratulations
[Laughter]
[Music]
yes by the end of the night
selector level
so
who is speaking who is soba
Jones that was because
wow
we're taking a breath we we're in shock
we did not expect this this is the
second year in a row sorry
we're taking our breath this is the
second draw in the second year in a row
that we have won this award uh and it's
it's we're really really humbled
Prudential thank you thank you thank you
we cannot believe it
um when I was coming here today I was
actually coming here to present to
represent our MD and also the HR
Director for Uganda breweries who's not
here with us today
but before I start let me get the whole
team to first introduce themselves
because I think they all deserve a
proper introduction so let me start from
the end so if you can just say your name
and what you do my name is Percy Jumba I
lead business Integrity team at Chicago
a very good evening to you all
right
well uh Joel kafir is my name I'm the HR
in charge of the also staff at Uganda
Brothers thank you
good evening ladies and gentlemen my
name is Judy I'm the HR business partner
for commercial thank you
I don't know what to say good evening
ladies and gentlemen my name is Dorcas
kayaga I'm the hrbp that is human
resource business partner for marketing
and I also deal with Employee Engagement
and endeavorment so the award we won is
on my head and I must say Prudential
Prudential thank you thanks a lot
good evening ladies and gentlemen my
name is Dora kukunda I'm HR business
partner I'm supporting supply thank you
okay last but not least my name is
jacket
and I manage corporate relations public
policy and Regulatory Affairs at Uganda
breweries before she takes the
microphone I just wanted to tell
honorable Minister that we are not
divorced like you said we are in love
I thank you so much and also just to
mention that we are the top three
taxpayers in Uganda
so we are growing our people
we are supporting over 40 000 Farmers
it's not about the celebration you're
seeing here the drinks flowing and
everything we are impacting lives
vulnerable Minister I thank you
for me sorry my name is Eunice I'm the
finance and strategy director at Uganda
breweries Limited
I'm the money person yeah so first
before I even say anything I think
um
we deserve to give a huge loud of
Applause to the almighty God for getting
us here today
we would not have done this without his
support
um his encouragement and you know always
uh
showing us the right direction so thank
you
um the other people that I would really
like to thank is all our customers our
consumers and of course not to forget
Prudential Prudential has really
supported us along the journey and we
thank you the Prudential team
I don't know where to begin
um you know we keep being told Africa is
the New Frontier for us Africa is
happening now and we are living
testimony of Africa happening now
um we have implemented so much in our
company as far as HR and people our
people are the most important thing in
our organization the biggest asset in
the organization
and as you can see inclusion and
diversity we've kind of taken over you
can see we have one man here so
inclusion and diversity is a big agenda
at Uganda breweries Limited
above and beyond that is all the work we
do behind ensuring our people are happy
with what they do every day they are
happy to wake up from their beds every
day and come to work yeah capability
building making sure mentally
health-wise that we have sorted them in
whichever way we can be able to is one
of our biggest strategy that we go by
every day and live by those rules on a
daily basis through the support of the
HR department
so for us I think it's just to to give a
huge thanks to everybody who has
supported us it's been a fantastic
Journey I'll tell you it's not easy to
do all the things that we do at Uganda
bear is limited but my HRT makes it look
so easy that everything has actually
come to play and come to place as it has
so for me I think it's to thank my team
here the whole HR team the whole CR team
our sales marketing the whole
organization there are the people who
have made this happen so thank you thank
you thank you
before you leave stage please uh if you
could if you could wait and we have all
the other winners join you we would like
every other winner that we have tonight
to please join
the rest on the platform all right you
got the worries first have your photo
uh overall winners
up close front stage front stage okay
corporate affairs
corporate Affairs wants the photo
cast
beautiful congratulations
Uganda breweries all the winners please
come to the stage all the winners come
with your award please
[Music]
my life
all the winners please come to the stage
I
am
with my guys
[Music]
simpler graphic systems
standby Bank absent Standard Chartered
Banks
come to the stage let's take a picture
and celebrate success you are VR please
come
overall government agency
hey let's balance the stage
[Music]
hey
we'll take the picture
yes those are the winners
MTN Uganda
congratulations
[Music]
overall winner 2022 back to back wins
fantastic
[Music]
I got
ta
[Music]
online
foreign
[Music]
then we shall go back
hey
yes
well done
all right let's jump in we have two
things to do before we let you go uh
allow me to welcome oh Apple macubia
the board chair of Prudential
what an evening
congratulations to the winners
Uganda breweries Limited
let's really be happy for them
I have been asked to
to come here and
make a vote of thanks and maybe propose
a toast
but before I do please join me
in thanking our guest of honor
honorable
show photography
did you know that
his name is
thank you thank you thank you honorable
for gracing our occasion
and for representing the right honorable
prime minister of Uganda
we want to thank all of you our partners
especially PWC
represented by ruthman
and the entire team
we want to congratulate all the winners
all the participants
I
want in a special way to congratulate
ubl
uh who who has got more than a minute I
think
simpler
stanbic if I don't say this I may get
into trouble
and so many other winners it's been a
lovely wonderful evening
and we can't be
happier for the outcome
but beyond the celebrations we we learn
lessons
on the best human resource practices
I don't want to repeat
what has been said already but we know
that the people
are the engines that drive our entities
our companies our country and we must
recognize them we must respect
we must support them and this is what
Prudential
Uganda and Prudential Global is all
about so join me in thanking our
representatives from Global Prudential
Africa
Maccabee is here
and and and we have other and I'm going
to read out countries so that you please
stand where wherever you are for
recognition we have representatives of
Prudential from Cameroon
the man who is handsome but also brainy
we have representatives from please sit
down
from Prudential Uganda the board
Rosemary and James
foreign
we have
Ace
majija Achu melee
Regional Ace was our
Prudential Uganda leader for some time
until he was promoted
we have Prudential from Singapore
we have Prudential from
Ghana I don't know who's here
but yes
we have Prudential Kenya from Kenya
please stand up if you're from Kenya
we have Prudential Nigeria
and Zambia please stand up for
recognition
so you can see that we have invested a
lot of
efforts and support from across the
continent
um
we have really really proud to be
associated with PWC and with this whole
mission of improving and recognizing uh
circumstances of our colleagues their
employees
now is the moment to request that
everyone fills their glasses
but perhaps before they do
I think that I may not
be forgiven if I do not in a special way
thank our masters masters of ceremony
please come closer
having they done a fantastic job
and the lady is not even wearing high
heels you can imagine
when that happens
should be a little taller
yeah when I wear the second pair
and when I'm lonely here
I think you are so kind about me but I
really appreciate that but whatever
the point is you Dior have done a
fantastic job and Prudential is very
very proud of your work thank you thank
you so may I request that you all fill
your glasses
and uh
I left my glass on the table
yes thank you
I'm going to request that we all stand
a man who is the bear of my glass is a
retired farmer he grows fish and and and
and coffee but ladies and Gentlemen
please raise your glasses
fast in appreciation of the work of the
government of Uganda in supporting and
recognizing the work of employees
the work of all of you who participated
in the survey
the work of PWC and Prudential
cheers
please enjoy the evening and thank you
very much
if you have a lot of energy in your hand
don't tears
you crush people's glasses
cheers ladies gentlemen have a great
night we still have a lot to drink so
please stay and enjoy and we have we
have amazing entertainment that we've
been serving for
the evening and we have amazing young
blood that is being backed all the way
from fennon
and
so he's single that's the first thing he
wants me to say before he steps on stage
so we have vamos 256 from fan on records
and this is just the beginning of the
night when he starts feed your grass and
make sure he dance back a last vamos
from fenon
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
I see
foreign
[Music]
someday
come on
[Music]
foreign
find me a story
[Music]
welcome
foreign
[Music]
come on
baby
[Music]
foreign
whoa whoa whoa
buddy
this is
cause you feeling
friends